

# António Chivela Kalumana

a.kalumana@outlook.com



+351 932291097

linkedin.com/in/antoniokalumana

### Summary

Hello! I'm Kalumana, a young professional with Cloud Engineer and software development experience in the Tech Industry. As a professional I've had experience at some organizations, all where I've been tied to Cloud providers, software development, agile methodologies, and project management. I'm passionate about working with teams to put forth the best product possible, ambitious, who knows how to get things done. Skills at backend and frontend frameworks, infrastructure as a code tools, cloud architecture, communication, teamwork, and proactive.

#### **Experience**



# Cloud Engineer

Claranet Portugal

Feb 2022 - Sep 2022 (8 months)

- Create Multi-cloud architecture "AWS e AZURE".
- Implementation of infrastructure as code using Terraform.
- Manage Infrastructures using Ansible.
- Automation infrastructure using Jenkins.
- Services Visualization using Amazon CloudWatch and Azure Monitor.

#### **Software Developer**

Bizdirect - A Claranet Group Company

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021 (5 meses)

- Design Web Interface and Mobile Interface with AdobeXD.
- Work with Backend and Frontend Frameworks using node.js and react.js.
- Relational Database using PostgreSQL.
- Rest API using Express.js.
- Postman to test API.

#### Education

Instituto Politécnico de Viseu

Licenciatura, Engenharia Informática Sep 2018 - Jun 2024

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals - Microsoft 992950756

## Languages

Português - Native English - Intermediate B2

### **Skills**

React Native • Python • Ansible • Git • JavaScript • HTML5 • Terraform • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • PostgreSQL • Microsoft Azure • AWS • Docker • Jenkins • MongoDB